Rootia shab teraba rabba dilbi erota sabu kuche bikara bikara bikura saru taruka molecase
OK
don't click on my little
Love
Support
thank you so much
Thank you
Vicki
about that
Hi
Sandy
My name is Doctor James
I'm the eye specialist
That's our first time
so don't worry
I'm a friend of your husband
OK
If you're ready
let's head into the clinic
OK
Please have a seat
I'm sorry but your husband will have to wait outside
I need to focus on my patient
OK
Thank you
OK zombies
So how long have you not been feeling well
Around 10 years
10 years
I see
And can you see these numbers on the blackboard here
OK
look at your eyes
Please let me take a quick look
OK
Thank you
One more check here
How many fingers am I holding up
No
no
it's only one figure
OK
I just need to check your temperature
I seem to have forgotten my thermometer
Could you take your mask off please and open your mouth
Let's use this